Seung Yoo

Visual / Product Designer

seungmyoo525@gmail.com Linkedin / Portfolio

ABOUT

Based in San Francisco and a community builder of Tech Women's Meetup. Experience in the education and design industry for years. Recently learned Frontend development to understand code and noticed I love design more than anything else. Currently, I'm exploring Product Design and am passionate about cultivating positive UX/ UI. Make it a creative way to solve real-world problems.

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer - Compass (SFUSD School management Platform) / GroupFive (Startup) 2023

- Designed mockups and Hi-fidelity for the web application and collaborate with engineers.
- Made design Flow, Components, variants and Design System.

UI, Frontend Engineer (Intern) - MLH fellowship - GitLab, Slippers(Pajamas) UI Design 2022 fall

Helped and improved several deliverables, built components for css framework in Version
 Control, Vue, Storybook, SCSS on the user experience of the GitLab Marketing Slippers
 Design System projects.

UI, Front-end Engineer & Co-organizer (volunteer) - Tech Girls Social in SF meetup 2021-2022

- Started the original group and assigned responsibilities to over 2000 people.
- Posted events to online forums and directed activities and workshops.
- Set up study groups: computer science algorithms, Team projects, UX/UI design

Designer, Visual / Character, illust - Grigon / Kobay 2007 - 2009

- Illustrating and visualizing and creating individual characters of games and animated characters to launch the games.
- cooperated with engineers and got aligned.

Teacher & Manager, International English kindergarten – JnE 2010 - 2016

- Ran and Grew a local classroom serving 5 to over 40 students.
- Organized special events and sent student progress reports.

EDUCATION	SKILLS	PROJECTS
MLH Fellowship - Open Source Track (Software Engineering), USA	Design Skills Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator HTML, CSS, SCSS, GitHub	Portfolio GroupFive (React, Figma) Site
FreeCodeCamp, Udemy- Full Stack Engineering, USA		
Soongeui College - Associate in Fine Arts and Design	Coding Skills Javascript, React, Vue, Storybook, Python	Tech Girls Social (Javascript and React) Site / Figma Mockup
KIDP - Visual Design Bootcamp, 2 year certificated		
National Open University- Early Childhood Education, BA		Sweet Store Project (Javascript and React) Site / Github Code

Site / Github Code